Radhika Naurvi

Address: L-38/B Sourabh Vihar , Badarpur New Delhi 110044

Cell:+91- 9999775648 radhikanaurvi93@gmail.c om

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Over 4+ years of IT experience which includes 3 experience in front end development. Seeking a position to utilize my skills & abilities in the Software Industry that offers professional growth while being resourceful & innovative. & I'm a Person with a positive attitude, Flexible extroverted nature. I have confidence in my values and beliefs and have an optimistic outlook towards life and give importance to integrity and commitment.

EXPERIENCE

AdGlobal360 India Pvt. Ltd, Noida — Frontend Developer

July 2021- Till Date

Designing and implementing user interface components for JavaScript web applications. Worked on a project **Nexa-MSIL**. Nexa MSIL is an end to end digital auto finance platform where the customer can view, compare and apply loan of their choice, and track the loan application in real time.

- Responsible for developing new user facing features using JavaScript.
- Building reusable components.
- Technology used: JavaScript, Gulp, Html5, Css
- IDE : Visual Studio

Audatex Solution Pvt. Ltd, New Delhi — Software Developer

Nov 2017- July 2021

- 1. Worked on a **Data Harvest** Project in which web Scraping of Canadian automobile websites was done by a java tool. Harvest 1000 websites & update tool according to requirement.
 - Technology used: Java, HTML, CSS
 - Jsoup to parse HTML Document.
 - Nightmare and Cheerio to parse Dynamic javascript websites.
 - Used Selenium webdriver to automate the scrolled webpage and save the webpage by using selenium Robot classes.
- 2. Worked on a Auda Call Project which is a web web application used for calling multiple automobile dealers, This application contains the record of dealers and the callers

SKILLS

Languages : HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery,

Bootstrap

Database: My SQL **Platform:** Windows 10

Pro

EDUCATION

Alagappa University

-- MCA- 2017

Lingaya's University

—BCA- 2013

Guru Harkrishan Public School
—Senior Secondary Examination

CBSE BOARD - 2010

Hemnani Public School

— Secondary Examination,
CBSE BOARD - 2008

Aricent Technologies pvt Pvt. Ltd, Gurugram — *Associate trainee(testing)*

March 2014- April 2015

Worked on a **GSMR Project** it's a wireless communication platform develop specifically for railway communication and application.

NALANDA-PRISM at ARICENT,

March - June 2014

Completed 3 Months professional training on software testing